Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[Hunting]
[Episode 6]
Do you want me to call again?
No need.
Send him a message.
What should I text?
Text what we told you.
My brother-in-law grows nice white tea
[Advanced Unit in Spiritual Civilization]
at home.
Is it from Matao Garden?
Give me some more.
Of course.
It's white tea.
Kui,
when handling tea in the future,
be mindful of your reputation.
What reputation?
It's grown by my own relatives.
Don't be so nervous.
Chief Fang,
well,
I wanted to talk about
the case of Mou Haidong.
You see,
for his son's sake,
he's not even afraid to harm himself.
What a ruthless person.
But regarding the drug maker,
he refused to say anything no matter what.
So I think this drug maker is
very important.
He must still have some hope
pinned on the drug maker.
Don't worry.
This drug maker
will definitely continue making drugs.
They need to fill their financial hole.
Think about it.
When people are pushed to the edge,
they'll always look for a way out.
So now this drug maker is the key.
They're manufacturing meth
on such a large scale.
Along this entire chain,
from production to storage,
and then to transportation,
I think we should
focus our investigation
on the raw materials.
What are you talking about?
Focusing on raw materials?
That'll take forever.
Kui,
use your brain.
Transportation.
Whether bringing in materials
or shipping out the product,
they always need transportation, right?
Right.
It's easier to start with transportation.
As it happens,
the guy who handled transportation
for Mou back then,
called Liu Bingqiang,
was caught by me.
He was very cunning.
The evidence chain wasn't complete then,
so he was released after just a few years.
I've been asking around.
These past years,
poeple say he's gone straight.
He started a legitimate
transportation company,
and even opened a restaurant.
I think we should investigate him.
I agree.
I just got a tip-off.
Liu Bingqiang
is recruiting people again.
That's good.
I'll follow up on him.
No, no, no.
You shouldn't follow up on this.
Dapeng has investigated him before
and has built up quite a few connections.
So,
he'll do it first.
You support him.
Fine, I'll support him.
Don't just answer me
so quickly.
No rash moves.
How could I be rash?
Dapeng's always the rash one.
Hurry up!
All the fish are dead.
You're giving me dead fish.
Who am I supposed to sell them to?
Hurry up!
Be careful with the scales.
The scales!
Poor appearance means poor price.
Come on, faster!
We're running out of time, Boss.
[Brother Qiang Freight Service]
What are you guys doing down there?
Get fishing!
Are you kidding me?
Can you please hurry up?
Hey, buddy.
It's Brother Qiang Freight Service?
What do you want?
Do you have odd jobs for me?
Looking for odd jobs?
Just trying to make some money.
Have you done dock work before?
I've worked on this dock for many years.
I'm Azhen.
Ask around. Everyone knows me.
Azhen.
I trust you.
Here's my number.
Call me later.
I'll contact you when there's work.
Thanks, buddy.
Thank you.
Take a look first.
No need to look.
I can do it.
I got it.
Have you done this before?
Of course.
Here.
Such fat black groupers!
There are two of them!
They are still alive.
Hey, watch the scales!
Careful with the skin.
Don't worry.
Don't damage the fish skin.
OK, no problem.
Don't worry. Don't get wet.
Don't get wet.
You guys down there, hurry up!
Come on!
Hurry up! If we can't ship these,
who am I going to sell them to?
Sorry. Sorry.
All the fish are going to be dead.
Hurry up!
Brother Qiang Freight Service
brings you good fortune.
Hello?
Hello,
Hao.
What's up, Lili?
What have you been busy with?
You haven't replied to any of my messages.
How's your grandmother doing?
Grandma's surgery went very well.
I was trying to reach you
to tell you about this.
That's good then.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you this time.
I can't take your money.
Why not?
Keep the money.
You have to take it.
I won't feel at ease unless you take it.
Please take the money.
Alright.
Then I'll give you a gift
in return.
Sure.
What kind of gift?
Where are you?
I'll bring it to you.
I'm at the 20-yuan Hostel.
What are you doing?
He hung up.
Kuang Bing,
check all hostels and apartments
with '20-yuan' in their names.
Got it.
We're on the run,
and you're telling others where we live?
What are you doing?
She's not "others". It's Lili.
She wants to give me a gift.
Lili?
How did she know you aren't home?
She's never been to my place.
Lili has never given you gifts before,
right?
You're overthinking.
She just wants to give me a gift.
Don't mess this up for me.
Give me my phone.
Come down.
We can't stay here anymore.
Let's go!
The number you have dialed is powered off.
Please try again later.
It's powered off.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I found it.
They must be staying at
the 20-yuan Hostel in Mawei District.
Let's go check it out.
By the way,
Wu Liang is still keeping watch there.
Tell him to go there too.
OK.
Got it.
Let's go.
We found them.
[Open]
[Closed]
Smelling good today, huh?
You're getting handsy.
You're being naughty.
I'll shower after you're done.
Hurry up!
Alright, I'll be there in a minute.
Did Xipi lose?
Serves him right.
I'll win it back when I return.
I'm telling you.
Jeez.
Stop showering! The police are coming!
Let's go!
The police are coming!
Go! This way!
Run! Run!
Move it!
Keep running forward!
Run!
Freeze!
-Stop!
Don't move!
Stop!
Come this way.
Don't move!
Run!
Don't run!
-Stop!
Freeze!
Got him!
Why are you arresting me?
Don't move!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Don't move!
[School Area]
Quick! Get in the car!
Stop!
Why did you save us?
Don't you recognize me?
Pigpen Boy.
You're Pigpen Boy from Fengmao Village.
Is it OK if I just drop you off here?
Yes.
What are your plans now?
No plans.
If you have nowhere to go,
you can turn to me.
Um,
doctor,
I...
Just call me Pharmacist Luo.
Pharmacist Luo,
could you lend us some money?
We're currently...
No need.
Really, it's not necessary.
It's OK.
I left in a hurry.
This is all I have.
No, please.
Don't worry.
Take it.
Is that OK?
Shut up.
What are you doing?
My friend’s got some labor work
that you can do.
If you're interested,
you can contact me.
My contact info is on the 709 game,
under the username "Pigpen Boy".
OK.
Thanks.
We'll definitely contact you.
We'll get in touch with you.
Thank you, Pharmacist Luo.
Bye.
Look at us, we're desperate now.
Finally someone wants to help us,
and you're acting all high and mighty.
Didn't you say he was
your childhood friend?
What are you talking about?
Do you know who he is?
Who is he?
Mou Haidong's illegitimate son.
Mou Hai...
Mou Haidong.
You mean that big drug dealer Mou Haidong
from Fengmao Village?
Then your childhood friend
must be very rich.
Do you believe me?
He might have been worse off than me
when he was a kid.
I'm heading back now.
OK, take your time.
Thanks.
Don't run.
No one will help you if you fall.
[Ancestral Hall of Mou Family]
Who told you to come here?
My mom.
Don't follow us!
[Mou]
Slow down!
That woman was his mother.
Even back then I felt the mother and son
were different from others.
Only when I grew up did I realize
his mother was making drugs.
In a pigpen?
Making drugs?
Wouldn't that stink terribly?
Everyone in the village despised them.
They said his mother was a slut,
and he was a bastard,
and also called him Pigpen Boy.
Mou Haidong was the same.
He'd beat and scold him whenever they met.
Mou even kept his mother
locked up in the pigpen.
He grew up in that kind of environment.
Wouldn't he turn into a psychopath?
I barely spoke to him.
I didn't really know him well.
But he...
he didn't seem like an evil person.
Anyway, after that,
I never saw him again.
Why?
My dad stopped shipping goods by boat.
Later on,
we rarely went to Fengmao Village.
Later I heard people say
his mother passed away.
His mother died?
How did she die?
I don't know.
It's probably good he left early.
Otherwise, he might have been arrested
by now.
He should be fine.
Gold-Tooth Wan's death
has nothing to do with him.
We can‘t do this and can't do that.
What can we do now?
Uncle has been arrested too.
I just want to work honestly,
and make some money
to leave this place.
Go somewhere I want to go,
and live the life I want to live.
Why is that so difficult?
I'm sorry, Duozai.
If I hadn't stolen those cans,
things wouldn't have turned out this way.
What if...
we turn ourselves in?
If we explain everything to the police,
would they believe us?
No way.
Absolutely not.
Turn ourselves in?
If we turn ourselves in
and the police think we're accomplices,
we'll go to jail.
And when I leave the jail,
who's going to give me back my youth?
No way.
Absolutely not.
I refuse to turn myself in.
Why don't we sneak across the border?
Let's get out of here
no matter what.
What do you think?
Crossing the border costs money too.
Didn't Pigpen Boy say
he'd find us some work?
You don't want his money,
but we can at least take money
that we earn with our own hands, right?
As you said,
he's Mou Haidong's illegitimate son,
an abandoned child.
He was beaten and scolded since childhood.
How could he teach him those things?
Didn't he say he went to school later?
He looks like a respectable person to me.
I haven't seen him for so many years.
He's just being loyal to an old friend.
What else would he want from us?
Our looks?
Or our wealth?
We're broke as hell now.
What could he possibly want from us?
Duozai,
you're just too stubborn sometimes.
You need to learn to be grateful.
Give me the phone now. I'll contact him.
I'll do it myself.
Fine.
Just make sure you contact him.
[Search]
[Pigpen Boy]
This is Duozai. I'm looking for a job.
[Send friend request]
[Send friend request] [Send]
[Pigpen Boy]
[Follow Your Heart sent a message.]
[World 709]
[You got a new message. Click to check.]
[Follow Your Heart]
I haven't seen any messages from you.
Are you having some problems?
I hope my intuition is wrong.
Hope everything goes well.
Remember to reply to me.
[Pigpen Boy is your friend now.]
[Follow Your Heart]
[Pigpen Boy]
Tell us what happened.
Officer,
I swear,
when I got there,
Gold-Tooth Wan was already dead.
The car was burning.
I'm telling the truth.
Mr. Zhen
can confirm everything I'm saying.
Listen,
don't dodge the important questions.
Why did you go down the mountain
with them?
Because,
there were goods
in that car down there.
Gold-Tooth Wan
made us take him to get the goods.
They threatened to kill us
if I didn't go.
I had no choice.
So we went down to get the stuff.
Weren't you making a deal?
There was no deal.
This is all I have.
These are all my possessions.
I don't have a penny to my name.
There was no deal.
If you weren't involved,
why did you run?
I was scared.
I mean,
it was serious.
Someone died,
and there were drugs involved.
I ran away because I was terrified.
Where did the goods come from?
Four-Eyes Hao.
[Recording]
He took
Xin Chuanyong's car
from a car dealership.
We had no idea there was meth in it.
It was completely accidental.
We had no clue.
Besides Mou Jiahao,
there was someone else, right?
Who?
Ma Duozai.
Ma Duozai, he...
Was he there? He...
I don't know if he was there.
Impressive.
How did you and your son
manage to keep your hands so clean?
Officer, I'm telling the absolute truth.
When we got there,
the car was burning.
And...
Gold-Tooth Wan was already dead.
I was standing there,
I was
completely stunned.
I had no idea what to do.
Continue.
Then suddenly it exploded.
Due to the explosion,
Mr. Zhen and I both passed out.
When I woke up,
Mr. Zhen
was lying there.
He seemed badly injured.
Officer,
how is Mr. Zhen?
Is he...
Stick to your own story.
When I saw that,
I was terrified,
so I ran away.
Well...
Officer,
I've told you everything I know.
So after you met with Mou and Ma,
what did you talk about?
I asked Hao
what happened.
Hao told me
that Gold-Tooth Wan wanted to kill him.
Gold-Tooth Wan
was high on drugs before,
really high.
He probably just fell by himself.
So, well...
Is that all?
Yes.
I know Hao
very well.
His legs aren't even as thick as my arms.
That knife was heavier than his hand.
He's real timid.
He wouldn't kill anyone.
Then who started the fire?
I don't know.
It was already burning when we got there.
Those electric cars on the street
sometimes catch fire by themselves.
So you mean
Ma Duozai wasn't at the scene?
I don't know.
If he was there,
and he saw me,
he could break my legs.
Listen,
don't try to be clever here.
Just tell the truth.
I didn't lie.
I've told you everything I know.
Everything you've told us
will be thoroughly investigated.
OK.
Mou Jiahao and Ma Duozai,
where are they hiding now?
You brought me here, so I don't know.
Then here's the deal.
Find them both
and bring them in.
I'll count it as redemption
for your crimes.
I'd like to help, but I don't even know
what crime I've committed.
Redemption for crimes...
Officer, you're
digging a huge pit
and asking me to jump in.
Ask them to come here and clear things up.
It's their only way out.
Wan Shan's death
has no official ruling yet.
If you really want to help them,
cooperate with us to find them.
Fine.
Officer, what does it mean
that his death has no official ruling yet?
Don't ask questions you shouldn't.
I've told you everything I know.
I've told you everything.
I can't make up things I don't know.
So you don't know?
I don't know.
That's fine.
If you don't know, just sit here.
Tell me when you remember something.
I've told you
everything I know.
Mr. Zhen?
What's your name?
I'm talking to you.
Are you dumb?
[Please put used paper in the bin,
and flush after use.]
Mr. Zhen,
why didn't you contact me
when you got out?
Didn't I tell you to contact me?
You did say you had connections.
Who knows if you were just bragging?
If I knew your connections were real,
I would've contacted you.
I didn't expect to see you here.
It must be fate.
Yes. Cheers.
I'm happy now.
This is so spicy.
I still remember
you helped me defeat the prison king.
I didn't have to clean the toilet anymore.
Why bring that up?
Someone like me
could look after you
while we were in there.
But once we're out,
educated people like you
can do much better than us.
I manage this transportation company.
If you want a desk job
with light duties,
just say the word.
No, no.
A guy like me
is good at moving stuff
and transporting goods.
Comfortable positions don't suit me.
I'm not used to that.
Mr. Zhen, what are saying?
Even at the docks,
you'd be a supervisor at least.
How could I let you be a cargo worker?
You really want to help me?
Yang Min, how about this?
Let me work with you.
We transport stuff and make quick money.
OK?
What's so funny?
Mr. Zhen,
I just got out.
Don't make me go back in.
I get it.
Forget I ever mentioned it.
Mr. Zhen.
What?
Let's drop it.
I'm trying to get through the hardship.
Life is
not easy.
No opportunities to make money.
No one is willing to hire someone like me.
Yang Min,
I've never asked you for anything.
But just now I did.
I need your help.
It's really tough.
I'm struggling.
I'm serious.
If you help me,
I'll remember this favor forever.
Mr. Zhen,
I'll see what I can find for you.
Keep your word.
Thanks, buddy.
Good.
I'll finish this drink.
[Brother Qiang Hot Pot]
I'm looking for Qiang.
Qiang!
Call Qiang.
Qiang.
Come and have a seat.
Make yourself at home.
Just relax.
The soup is good.
Help yourself to some soup.
I'll do it myself.
Take more.
Jiamin.
It's delicious.
I used to make this soup myself.
It tasted so much better than this.
I know.
Yang Min often talked about you in there.
You love delicious food.
You love rules.
You're a very meticulous person.
I know.
What did you say your name was?
What's your name again?
Yang Shu.
You can call me Azhen.
He works in transportation.
He always looked after me in there.
Very reliable.
Yes.
Transportation, huh?
I know all transportation guys
in this area.
How come I've never heard of you?
My guys all started
with box trucks doing odd jobs.
We don't work fixed routes.
That's not working in transportation.
That's just freelancing.
Qiang, that's not how we put it.
My guys and I
started with street vending.
Our connections are just as extensive.
Neighborhoods, back roads,
highways, and national roads,
we know them all well.
How many routes do you operate now?
We don't have many people,
about six or seven guys.
What's your rate?
Easy.
With Yang Min involved,
I'll give you a discount.
Let's drink soup.
OK.
Cheers!
Zhi'an.
Every time I call you, you're always busy.
Have you forgotten about your friends?
Exactly.
Yeah, it's been a long time.
Exactly!
Right.
You never visit us.
An,
you should drink three cups as a penalty.
I know. I know.
Drink up.
I've been really busy with work lately.
I'll take three drinks.
And today is my treat.
I'm watching you.
Yu, pour her a drink.
Keep an eye on her.
Drink up, An.
Come on, drink this.
You drink with her.
You're just trying to get out of drinking.
-She doesn’t drink.
-She drank it.
You won't even drink the first cup, An.
Let me see the phone.
What's wrong?
Why are you taking my phone?
What are you doing? Drinking or not?
-Stop playing with the phone.
-Yeah.
We rarely get to see each other.
She's just making excuses.
Exactly. She never drinks.
You guys enjoy.
Where is she going?
Where are you going?
Captain Luo,
they're making a deal
at the night market in Dianqian Village.
Can you check this car?
The plate number is 77H32.
[Brother Qiang Hot Pot]
Uncle Yang,
what are you doing here?
What happened to you?
You've got the wrong person.
Uncle Yang,
where have you been all these years?
Mom said you never came home.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Stop following me around.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Go away.
Uncle Yang.
The neighbor's daughter keeps stalking me.
I don't know why.
Who is this?
A friend.
If I don't follow you,
you'll just hang out with such bad people.
Isn't that right?
Neighbor's daughter?
After the divorce,
you wanted to abandon your own child, too?
Yes, I don't want to see either of you.
Just get out of here.
Fine.
Then don't come looking for us anymore.
Wait.
What's all this shouting?
Enough.
-What's wrong?
-Qiang.
This is Mr. Zhen's daughter.
Azhen's daughter has grown into a lady.
Since she's already here,
we should treat her.
Azhen, you two should stay.
The kid knows nothing.
It's alright.
We're all family here.
Come on, young lady.
Come in, come in.
Let's talk inside.
Why make a scene out here?
Come in and talk.
What is this?
Listen,
if you dare touch meth,
I'll call the police on you immediately.
Don't talk nonsense.
We're eating.
This young lady
is quite impressive.
Azhen,
your daughter doesn't look like you.
It's embarrassing to say,
but when my wife married me,
she brought this burden along.
How could she look like me?
That's quite something of you.
Young lady,
now you're here,
and you're so pretty,
but I don't even know your name.
Let me see your ID.
Are you a cop?
You want to check my ID?
I didn't take it with me.
Whether I'm a cop or not,
you're in my house now.
Let me see it.
What are you doing?
Let go of my hand!
Step aside.
I got this.
I'm leaving, Zhi'an.
Bye.
[Police ID]
She didn't bring her ID.
Get away!
Back off!
Let go!
Don't touch me!
Get away!
She came prepared,
and it's even pink.
Let me tell you,
this spray
is made to deal with people like you.
Qiang,
stop it.
You're scaring the kid.
And you
just tell Qiang your name.
She has my surname.
Yang Ying.
Azhen,
since this is our first cooperation,
we need to know more about each other.
Don't be upset.
No, no, not at all.
So, Qiang,
if you've asked everything you needed to,
are we done?
Can she leave now?
Azhen,
we're about done talking.
Take your daughter home.
I'll contact you if anything comes up.
OK.
Let's go.
Come on.
See you later, Qiang.
Qiang,
are we still going to use him?
He already knows what we do.
Use him or not, we should check him out.
Follow them.
Why did you talk to me?
I didn't know you were on a mission.
And anyone who sees you
looking so miserable
would be curious, OK?
What do you mean miserable?
You have no perception at all.
I have no perception?
Why are you so ungrateful?
At least I helped you
get through that crisis.
I wasn't in any crisis.
If I hadn't been there just now,
wouldn't they have forced you to take it?
I can solve my own problems.
I don't need your help.
Fine.
I won't interfere anymore.
You're so great.
What's so great about me?
Now I suddenly have a daughter
out of nowhere.
One lie leads to a hundred more.
I didn't know I was supposed to be
your neighbor's daughter.
So I could only
pretend to be your daughter, right?
Fine, good job.
But anyway,
good thing you cut a hole in my pocket.
Otherwise they would've found my badge.
Isn't everything resolved now?
Why are you sighing?
There's a black Passat behind us.
It has been following us all the way.
You see it?
What should we do?
Call Luo Zhongkui.
Request backup.
Tell him we're heading home now.
OK.
Alright, stop hiding.
Come out now.
You're still shouting?
What are you doing here?
This is a coincidence.
Dapeng.
Good. You've improved.
You even know to call for backup now.
It's to protect her.
Everything's ready.
Let's go.
Move.
Wait.
There are people tailing us downstairs.
Won't we run into them if we leave now?
I know,
but you're even less safe here.
Let's put on some disguises.
I have a place to hide.
Hello,
you clean all this area?
Yes, I clean it all.
That's hard work.
Do you know the father and daughter
who just went upstairs?
Father and daughter?
That messy guy on the second floor
is often not home.
I've never seen his daughter.
Not even once?
Never seen her.